{
    "id": "f5b6749b8968402798536525f45da7d0",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I .......................... to go many days ago.",
            "description": "We use the simple past tense with past time expressions like ago. ",
            "answers": [
                "decided",
                "have decided",
                "am deciding"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Only ............................... people attended the meeting.",
            "description": "We use 'a few' to mean 'some'. Few means almost none. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was late but ........................... were on time.",
            "description": "Either 'others' or 'other people' is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "others",
                "others people",
                "other people"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked his opinion ............................... not to offend him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "so as",
                "so as that"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Maria, ......................... is on holiday at the moment, is my neighbor.",
            "description": "We cannot use 'that' in non-identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I worked ........................... long.",
            "description": "We do not use articles in the expression 'all day'. ",
            "answers": [
                "the all day",
                "all day",
                "all the day"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They ................................ the station before I arrived.",
            "description": "We do not use prepositions after reach. ",
            "answers": [
                "reached",
                "reached to",
                "reached at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I had an enjoyable day ........................ I was one of the winners.",
            "description": "Because is a conjunction. Because of is a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... children like chocolates.",
            "description": "No article is used before most when we generalize things. ",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I visited them ...........................",
            "description": "No article or preposition are used before expressions like next week, last month, next day etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "last month",
                "the last month",
                "in last month"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't know ......................... I will be able to come.",
            "description": "We can use if or whether to introduce indirect questions. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It is time she .................................. to bed.",
            "description": "We use past tenses after 'it's time' with present or future reference. ",
            "answers": [
                "has gone",
                "goes",
                "went"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}